- Deep in the woods.
there lies a secret door.
and behind it. nightmares.
No!
Real nightmares.
I belong to a colony
that has sworn for centuries
to guard this door
and to protect our world
from the horrors
that lie behind it.
[banging on door]
It is my duty.
and I cannot fail.
[banging continues]
[breathing heavily]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
[screams]
[banging continues]
[ominous music]
[birds caw. animal bleats]
[hammering]
[indistinct chatter]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[children laughing]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
[loud hammering]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Shh!
All right. listen close.
Count to 100 after I leave
and then go to the council.
Tell them that Disciples
have been hurt.
Can you do this?
Warmth to you.
- Carrie?
Carrie Ecker?
Hey. there.
why aren't you at your post?
♪ ♪
Carrie!
- Carrie!
- Get back here. Carrie Ecker!
- [panting]
- Hey!
♪ ♪
[indistinct shouting]
- [shouts]
[breathing heavily]
- This way. follow me.
Quickly!
[indistinct shouting]
- She's close.
- Let's go.
[distant shouting]
- [gasps]
[bird screeches]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[engine rumbles]
[dark rock music]
♪ ♪
- This is how we dance...
- In West Pine!
[both grunting]
Like this. Like this.
Both: This is how
we eat in West Pine.
["Never Never" by Scout]
- Mmm!
- Ah!
You want to get a fresh egg...
[both laugh]
And then pour
your artisan toppings.
♪ ♪
both: This is how we express
our emotions in West Pine.
[guns popping]
- Why isn't anyone
watching these?
We're literal comedic geniuses.
- Because no one knows
what West Pine is.
- It's a town.
They get the concept.
Like. I need to be famous fast
so I don't have to get a job
selling diapers and Vaseline.
- Eh. make an OnlyFans.
- You make an OnlyFans.
- Also. what do you even
put on your résumé?
You haven't done shit.
- Skilled in math.
spreadsheets. dance.
- [chuckles] Okay. dance.
And cashiers
don't make spreadsheets.
- Wha... okay.
Well. a robber comes in
and is like.
"Bitch. organize my data!"
I don't know.
- ♪ Don't need to assure you ♪
♪ That I was wrong ♪
- Unrealistic.
Robbery is far too interesting
for West Pine.
- Bro. you're about to be on TV.
Stop pretending
that's not interesting.
- Not the kind of interest
that I want.
- Maybe your parents would stop
putting everyone
out of a job. then.
- I will murder you.
like. actually.
- Look. all I'm saying is.
if I'm gonna
stare into the void all day.
I might as well get paid for it.
- Ooh. ow.
- Make some rent
for when we graduate
and can get
the fuck out of here.
- [sighs] But then I won't
get to stare
into the void with you.
- Wow. you Frisks
really hate jobs.
[knock at door]
- For the billionth time. Nolan.
[music stops]
[indistinct shouting outside]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Hey. Lumi.
You ready to get on camera?
- There's something out there.
- Come on.
Hold up your sign. baby.
- The dead girl is me.
- [chuckles] Okay.
That deserves a chocolate.
[chuckles]
- There he is.
[indistinct chatter]
- Would you like to take
another four hours?
We can wait.
Why the earring?
- Why the dye job?
- Women suffer enough
for the vanities.
Now the boys want in. too?
- I just wanted to pizzaz you
on your big day.
- [scoffs] Get beside your dad.
You're distracting.
Seriously.
- I'm here at the home
of Victoria Frisk...
Lawyer behind
the high-profile suit
against West Pine Nickel...
As she celebrates the closure
of one of the mine's tunnels.
- Gallery eight was dumping
acid runoff
right into our drinking water.
I can't say I'll miss that.
But our work isn't over.
So long as WPN operates.
we tempt fate.
[voice fades slightly]
We're inviting a blight
onto our town...
One that will drive our children
to sickness and death.
History is defined
by those who act
in the face
of intense opposition
simply because
they know it's right.
[car horn honks]
- Calm mind. steady hand.
Calm mind. steady hand.
[metal clatters]
[laughter]
Excuse me. sir.
Do you know where I might find
a bus to Salem?
- Front of grocery. on the hour.
- Do you know when might be?
- Your religious group
not teach you to read?
Look at the schedule.
[laughter]
[ominous music]
- I'll take this to the back
for Lee to review tomorrow.
- Appreciate you. Thanks.
[door opens. bell jingles]
Hey.
Are you all right?
[tense music]
- Have you seen this girl?
♪ ♪
- Hi. sir.
How can I help you?
- Just looking.
♪ ♪
- Go. go.
[bell jingles]
Something for your kids.
[chuckles]
[bell jingles]
[footsteps approaching]
- [shouts]
- Hi.
Sorry.
Uh. cool if I join?
You're from
the Disciples of Dawn. right?
You. um. running
from the colony?
Like... like. leaving them?
We don't see y'all much.
[chuckles]
Here.
- Oh.
- I'm Tasha.
- Thank you for helping me.
- Uh. i-it's yours...
A gift between new friends.
Although friends usually know
one another's names.
- Carrie.
My name is Carrie.
- Cute name.
Carrie...
I think you might need
a disguise.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Five. four.
three. two. one.
Ready or not. here I come!
♪ ♪
Snowball. you freaky bitch.
We both got our cages. huh?
Gonna find you. Lumi!
You can't hide from me.
you little bug.
[door creaks]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Here I come!
- [giggles]
- Lumi!
I'm gonna find you.
♪ ♪
Lumi?
- Hello.
♪ ♪
- Gonna get you. Lumi!
Gonna find you.
♪ ♪
[alarm beeping]
[thudding]
- Shoes.
Shoes off.
Dad's never seen
a Sharper Image catalog
he didn't love.
[beeping continues]
- [computerized voice] Disarmed.
- The living room has taken
a real man cave sort of aura
since Mom died.
Not sure if Disciples. like.
bathe or whatever.
but feel free.
Red's hot. blue's cold.
Are you okay figuring it out?
I know you haven't spent
much time in the real world...
- We're not as blind
as you might think.
- Right. no. I didn't mean.
like. you don't. like...
- You'd be surprised
what the real world looks like.
- Uh. clean towels are here.
Um...
- [chuckles]
- Just gonna...
Oh. okay.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- [giggles]
- [sobbing]
[shower creaks. pops]
[creak. pop]
[shouts in pain]
♪ ♪
[stick thud echoing]
[keys clacking]
♪ ♪
- "Anti-technological"?
- Thank you for the wash.
- Oh. Okay.
I put some. uh. clothes
over there.
Yeah.
[chuckles]
[scissors snipping]
- [breathes deeply]
Would your father be able
to take me to Salem tonight?
- Uh. you know people in Salem?
- I-I was told
that I could disappear there.
- Yeah.
We can figure something out.
Are the scars from them?
The Disciples?
We don't hear much
about you guys.
I mean. kids tell stories.
but kids also chug cough syrup.
[laughs]
So...
Just curious why y'all live
out in the woods like that.
- It's to protect you...
so you don't have to know
what we know
about the dangers
that go on out there.
- Like what. Bigfoot?
Sexy werewolves?
- Your eyes are very yellow.
- It's my signature look...
Electric.
Do you want to try?
They'd never recognize you.
[upbeat rock music playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I never thought you'd ever ♪
♪ Show up. show up. show up ♪
♪ But look at you now ♪
♪ I never thought you'd ever ♪
♪ Blow up. blow up. blow up ♪
♪ Just take a look at you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Just take a look at you now ♪
- [whistles]
- Lumi. babe!
- Lumi!
[whistles]
- Go for the tree line!
- Lumi!
Oh. my God.
- Hey.
Do you think it might be
an angry miner?
One of your ex's friends?
- [whistles]
- She's not a dog. Gordon!
- Where is she?
[sobs]
- No. no. no.
- Lumi!
[sobbing]
Lumi.
Lumi!
- Lumi!
[indistinct shouting]
- I'll go down here.
Lumi!
- Lumi!
- Where are you?
- Hello!
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[twig snaps]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Ah. New Colony. who dis?
You like?
- [laughs]
Yes.
Uh. maybe less colors.
[sniffs]
[perfume spritzes]
Oh.
Is that pickles?
- Sandalwood.
It doesn't hurt to try. right?
Disciples don't use internet.
do you?
- Hmm?
[camera shutter clicks]
[knock on window]
Oh!
You're safe.
Oh. it's okay!
Nolan's a friend.
You will never guess
what's going on.
- Lumi's missing.
- Wait. what?
- I was supposed
to be watching her
I-I'm freaking out.
Is Khalil home?
- No. but he's about
to get off work.
There's something
I have to tell you...
- Everybody blames me.
which may be valid...
I was so stoned. but...
[whispering]
I'm actually scared.
Like. I think something bad
might have really happened.
- Oh. my God.
- Just...
This was on a tree. like.
20 feet from my house.
Evil. right?
A-a-and I heard this. like.
freaky. like. whistling sound.
- What?
- I don't know.
- Are... you... ready?
- For... Fat... Freddy's!
Dad. you get disco fries?
[whispering]
Don't hide in there.
Go under the bed.
No. no. don't.
- Why?
- Go under the bed.
Go under the bed.
- [sighs]
What the f... [muffled shout]
- Do I look like a joke to you?
- What?
- Hell. yeah. I got disco fries.
- [chuckles]
- [muffled shout]
- What was that sound?
- What was what sound?
- Well. hello. there.
You with him?
[cell phone vibrates]
- Saw you on the telly. Nolan.
Nice of you to pay us a visit.
Take in the sights before your
parents put us all out of work
- I'm not my family. Rhys.
- So you're cool with WPN. then?
Chill with the mine?
Maybe you should talk
to your parents or something.
[heavy metal playing
through earbuds]
♪ ♪
- What I can't stand. Tasha.
is when you so audaciously
defy my rules.
- His cousin is missing.
- Probably out
hugging a tree somewhere.
She's a Frisk.
- She's probably
cold and scared. actually.
- Oh. speaking of. Carrie.
my friend's girl volunteers
at a church in Salem.
helps runaways.
I'll take you there
before work tomorrow. okay?
They'll help you make a whole
strategy for reintegrating...
Work. all that.
- Her strategy is Salem tonight.
Let's give her money and a ride.
- What money. baby?
Medical debt.
- Sell the massage chair.
- I'll sell you first.
- Tomorrow's fine.
I want to help your friend
search for their family tonight
as a thank-you for helping me.
Mmm.
[chuckles]
- I respect a woman who eats.
You ready for round two?
- Mm-hmm.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- Tasha. your friend shows
his face on our block again.
I'll rip his
gay little earring off.
- You're tough. Rhys.
How cool.
- Hey. strong features. Tasha.
- Still in high school. Spoons.
- Not bad.
[laughter]
- Tasha. my dear friend.
my muse.
who's she?
- I'm Carrie Ecker.
I'm going to find your cousin.
♪ ♪
[bird hoots]
- Okay. did the pumpkin-humpers
take Lumi? I'm confused.
- Don't call the Disciples
"pumpkin-humpers."
What does that even mean?
- It means one who
humps pumpkins in woods.
Wouldn't want to offend
my cousin's kidnapper.
- It wasn't the colony. but
we've dealt with this. too.
- Oh. good.
- Let's see what turns up.
Who knows?
- I'll split off.
You two go ahead.
We'll cover more ground.
[insects chirping]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[exhales deeply]
To vast Gehenna I give my skin.
pray. warm shadow. let me in.
♪ ♪
[sound muffles]
[heart beating]
[muffled]
Calm mind. steady hand.
[heart beating]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[twig snaps]
[shouts]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful note]
[shouts]
- [screeches]
- [grunts in pain]
♪ ♪
Come. demon!
Get your blood!
[grunts]
[screaming]
- Um...
- [screaming]
- Carrie?
Who are you?
♪ ♪